College English test band six.
Part two listening comprehension.
Section a directions.
In this section, you will hear two long conversations.
At the end of each conversation, you will hear four questions.
Both the conversation and the questions will be spoken only once.
After you hear question, you must choose the best answer from the four choices marked A B C and d.
Then Mark the corresponding letter on answer sheet one with a single line through the centre.
Conversation one wow I would give anything to be more like audrey hepburn I never really understood why so many girls were such big fans of her.
I mean I've seen the famous films Roman holiday breakfast at Tiffany's and a few others.
But I still do.